tentlan.com 2015-05-22

# Tentlan

Protection of your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy will inform you about the personal data that is collected in the context of our services and how it is processed and used.

## General Information

This Privacy Policy applies to all online games ("hereafter "games") of Lionmoon UG (limited liability), hereafter "Lionmoon", and all websites of Lionmoon. In case you make use of services provided by third parties, the privacy policies of these third parties apply exclusively. Lionmoon does not verify privacy policies of third parties.

We collect, process and use personal data according to the Federal Data Protection Act (German: BDSG), the Telecommunications Act (German: TMG), other mandatory legal provisions where applicable, as well as on the basis of consent of the respective person.

## Collection of Data

Generally, you can access our services without disclosing any personal data. If you register on our websites and/or games, or if you would like to use our paid services, it will be necessary to provide personal data. We collect personal data that you voluntarily communicate to us electronically or in any other way when registering on our websites or in our games, when contacting us, participating in promotional actions, surveys, raffles, or when subscribing to our newsletter. Furthermore, we collect personal data inasmuch as this is necessary for the provision of services or for their payment. This includes in particular a handling of your payment orders. This data may include, for example, your name, address, e-mail address and other personal data which Lionmoon may query in individual cases. For a registration as a user, it is only necessary to provide an e-mail address, password and possibly a player name.

In the context of using our games and websites we additionally collect the following protocol data: name of the visited website, date and time of visits, duration of visit on our websites, IP address that you use to contact us, as well as system data. We use the protocol data only for statistical evaluations in order to ensure the operation, security and optimization of the services. In doing so, no use of data related to personal identification takes place. However, we reserve the right to review the protocol data if there is a founded suspicion of an abusive use based on concrete evidence. 

## Cookies

In order to feature our offering of services in the most user-friendly, efficient and secure way, we use, as many other companies, so-called cookies. Cookies are small text files which are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Cookies neither damage your computer, nor do they contain any viruses. We employ both so-called "session-cookies" and permanent cookies. We use "session cookies" to facilitate you a user-friendly navigation through our websites and/or games, or to facilitate your correct authentication. After your visit to our websites, the "session cookies" are automatically deleted from your hard drive. Permanent cookies are stored over a longer period of time on your hard drive. We can use them e.g. to enable an auto-login so that you can save your time when filling out forms and/or access our websites and/or games next time. We do not relate the data stored in cookies with your personal data you provide us on a voluntary basis, which we are entitled to collect, process and use for other purposes. **You can reject the acceptance of cookies or delete permanent cookies. For this, please follow the instructions of the manufacturer of your browser.** Please note that in this case you may no longer be able to use our websites and/or games or only in a limited manner for technical reasons.

## Use of Data

If you order our services, we collect, store and use your personal data only insofar as it is necessary to render our services and fulfill the contract. This also includes the use of your stored data for all kind of use related to handling of your contract about the use of services (e.g. use of games and/or other services, participation in chats, blogs, discussion forums); for providing information related to offer and registration such as adjustments of our offer, extensions/updates, online shop or technical issues, as well as details for the processing of payments. Furthermore, we use your data to communicate with you. This includes in particular providing you assistance and support, as well as providing you with important information about your contract.

If you provide your e-mail address in the context of the existing customer relationship, we may inform you by e-mail about the news of our product range such as products, services and certain events, that are similar to those products/services of Lionmoon you have already made use of. As a matter of course, you may withdraw your consent for it in written form (e.g. by e-mail) at any time, thereby no costs other than transmission costs of the withdrawal at the base rates (i.e. the costs of your Internet, e-mail, mobile or phone connection) may arise. In every communication and in every newsletter that you receive from Lionmoon you will have a possibility to reject to receive any further information and send a revocation to this respect.

Beyond the extent permitted by legal provisions for the purposes of advertising and/or market and opinion research, we furthermore collect, process and use your personal data only if you have consented to collecting, processing and using it for the aforementioned purposes. In this way, we may occasionally ask you to provide your data in the context of a survey. You are free to decide if you wish to participate in such surveys and if you wish to provide the data. The survey data will be used to improve the use of our websites, products and services.

We may also offer the users a possibility to use a recommendation service for products and services of Lionmoon in some of Lionmoon's games. With providing an e-mail address or a social network account of the recipient by the user, the recipient will receive a one-time invitation leading to the offer of Lionmoon. We process thus provided personal data only to send this one-time e-mail or message and, if necessary, to enable the blocking of further messages of this kind.

Moreover, we use your data in anonymous way for statistical analysis in order to improve our offer and adjust it to the needs of users. No transmission of the data to any third party takes place.

Finally, we use your data in order to protect our websites and our games against abusive use and to trace any unauthorized access.

## Transmission of Data

The disclosure of your personal data generally only takes places with your express consent. The exception thereof is the data transmission to our service partners, in particular to those that handle payment transactions, such as credit card companies, providers of prepaid cards, of mobile services, etc., or providers that create and process statistics and IT service providers (such as data centers, hosting providers, backup services, database services), provided that and insofar as it is necessary to fulfill the contract with the partner or to hinder and clarify fraud cases. These service providers are obligated to handle your personal data according to this Privacy Policy and the applicable data protection laws. Also, your personal data may be disclosed in individual cases if required by law.

## Google Analytics

Our websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, which are text files placed on the user's computer, to help to analyze how users use these websites. The information generated by the cookie about the use of these websites by the user (including the user's IP address) will generally be transmitted to and stored by Google on a server in the United States. Through activating the IP anonymizer on these websites, however, your IP address will be shortened beforehand by Google within member states of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the whole IP address be transferred to a Google server in the USA and shortened there.

Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the websites, to assemble reports on website activity for website operators and provide other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. 

Google will not associate your IP address as transmitted by Google Analytics with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of these websites. You can, at any time with effect for the future, object to the collection and storing of data for the purpose of web analysis by installing the browser add-on to deactivate Google Analytics (the link to the site is <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>).

## Use of Social Media Plugins

Our websites may use social plugins of social networks such as, for example, Facebook, Twitter or Google+.

If you visit a website of our online offer that contains such a plugin, the respective plugin will be activated and a connection to the servers of the corresponding social network will be established. It will herewith be transmitted to the server of the respective social network which of our websites you have visited. Provided that you click one of the aforementioned links while visiting our website, and are logged into your personal account at the respective social network, the respective social network can associate your visit to the website with your social network account. When interacting with the plugins (e.g. by clicking the button “Like” on Facebook or entering a comment), the corresponding information can be associated with your user account with the respective social network , which you can prevent by logging out of your account before you start using the plugins. 

For further questions pertaining to the collection and use of data by social networks, as well as regarding your rights and possibilities to protect your privacy, you will find in the privacy declarations of the respective social networks.

## Links

Our offer may contain links to external pages of third parties. By clicking on those links you abandon our websites and will be redirected to websites of third parties, for whose contents, observance of data protection and for whose privacy policy we are not responsible. This Privacy Policy only applies to websites and games of Lionmoon and not to websites of third parties. We therefore recommend you to carefully read privacy policies of the linked websites.

## Revocation of Consent

If you have consented that we may process your personal data, you may revoke your consent at any time. Insofar as your revocation refers to the receipt of newsletters or other e-mails, you will be informed as a part of the communication that you may cancel your subscription at any time. The cancellation of your subscription will cause you no costs other than the transmission costs stated in the base rates.

## Deletion of Data

Unless you have explicitly consented to any other use of your data, your personal data will be deleted after the contract has completely been fulfilled and after the period for the storage of data according to the requirements by commercial and tax laws has expired.

## Right to Request Information

You may receive at any time and without giving reasons free of charge information about all your personal data stored by us, whereby no costs other than transmission costs at the base rates may arise. You may ask us at any time to block, correct or delete your personal data collected by us. Please use the contact address indicated in the section "Contact for Privacy Policy". 

## Data Security

We secure our websites, games and other systems with technical and organizational measures against any loss, destruction, access, changes and distribution of your data by unauthorized persons. Though we constantly undertake control measures, a complete protection against all kind of risks that may arise cannot be guaranteed. For this reason, sensitive data should not be transferred in the first place or should only be transferred via secure and/or encrypted connection.

We process your personal data in compliance with German Data Protection Law. When submitting payments, the transfer of your data is protected by SSL encryption technology.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to adjust this Privacy Policy at any time. We will inform you about such changes with appropriate means.

### Contact for Privacy Policy

For questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Lionmoon UG (haftungsbeschraenkt)  
Hermann-Hesse-Platz 7  
76669 Bad Schoenborn  
Germany  
E-mail: legal@lionmoon.com  
Fax: 0049 (0) 7253 845-0809 

This Privacy Policy is valid as of September 30, 2014, version 1.0.
